ufindbook.com 2009-06-26

# User Login | Download Free eBooks

Thank you for visiting uFindBook.com Website and reviewing our privacy policy. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

**Cookies**

We do not use "persistent" web cookies. Persistent web cookies are defined as web cookies that can track "the activities of users over time and across different web sites.

**Emails and Web Forms**

Personally identifying information that you provide by email and/or web forms will be used only for such purposes as are described at the point of collection (for example on a web form), such as to send information or products to you, process your application, or to respond to your questions or comments.

If you provide contact information, uFindBook.com may contact you to clarify your comment or question, or to learn about your level of reader satisfaction with our website. We do not sell any personal information to third parties.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our policy discloses the privacy practices uFindBook.com (www.ufindbook.com). But uFindBook provides links to other web sites.

When you leave our web site (www.ufindbook.com), you will go to sites outside our control. These external sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies and procedures described here for uFindBook.com do not apply to any external links. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any site linked from ours, especially if you share any personal information.

Be informed. You are the person best qualified to protect your own privacy.
